Alright, juggling three clubs, alright we discussed how to hold two in one hand. We discussed every aspect. Now, it's the time to do it.
Okay, it's just like juggling three balls except you have to be careful because if you throw them so that they will go away from your body or towards your body, there's a much greater chance of you hitting yourself in the face.
I've been hit in the mouth.
I've been hit in the eye.
I had seen people do both and it hurts.
So, you got to be careful when you first start okay and it's like most things not as hard as it looks to you when you first start.
It's way slower than you think but this is how it looks okay.
If you notice, it's nice, slow, single rotations.
If I stand sideways, you'll get a better look.
They're nice, slow, single rotations and it's not because of how I'm spinning them, it's because of how high I'm throwing them.
Of course, it is possible to spin them faster but like I said before it's not necessary.
Spinning them faster is another trick in itself just throwing them is hard enough for most people.